Lowell Thomas Papers: Periodicals
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
- 3. The Geographical Journal, 1924-1982; 4 boxes
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXIX No. 5, May 1927 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXIX No. 6, June 1927 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXX No. 1, July 1927 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXX No. 2, August 1927 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXX No. 4, October 1927 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXX No. 6, December 1927 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXI No. 1, January 1928 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXI No. 2, February 1928 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXI No. 4, April 1928 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXI No. 5, May 1928 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXII No. 1, July 1928 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXII No. 2, August 1928 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXII No. 3, September 1928 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXII No. 4, October 1928 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXII No. 5, November 1928 (Box 12)
  - Memorandum by the Council of the Royal Geographical Society on Project for Hall and Library, 1928 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIII No. 1, January 1929 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIII No. 2, February 1929 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIII No. 3, March 1929 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIII No. 4, April 1929 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIII No. 5, May 1929 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIII No. 6, June 1929 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIV No. 1, July 1929 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIV No. 2, August 1929 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIV No. 3, September 1929 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIV No. 6, December 1929 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXV No. 1, January 1930 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXV No. 2, February 1930 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXV No. 3, March 1930 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXV No. 4, April 1930 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXV No. 6, June 1930 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXVI No. 1, July 1930 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXVI No. 2, August 1930 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXVI No. 3, September 1930 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXVI No. 4, October 1930 (Box 12)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXVII No. 1, January 1931 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXVII No. 5, May 1931 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXVII No. 6, June 1931 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXVIII No. 1, July 1931 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXVIII No. 5, November 1931 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIX No. 1, January 1932 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIX No. 3, March 1932 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIX No. 4, April 1932 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXIX No. 5, May 1932 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXII No. 1, July 1933 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXII No. 2, August 1933 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXII No. 6, December 1933 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXII No. 4, April 1934 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXII No. 5, May 1934 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXIV No. 1, July 1934 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXIV No. 4, October 1934 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXV No. 1, January 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXV No. 2, February 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXV No. 3, March 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXV No. 4, April 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXV No. 5, May 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVI No. 1, July 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVI No. 2, August 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVI No.3, September 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVI No. 4, October 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVI No. 5, November 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVI No. 6, December 1935 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVII No. 1, January 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVII No. 2, February 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVII No. 3, March 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVII No. 4, April 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVII No. 5, May 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVII No. 6, June 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVIII No. 1, July 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVIII No. 2, August 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVIII No. 4, October 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVIII No. 5, November 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXVIII No. 6, December 1936 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXIX No. 1, January 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXIX No. 2, February 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXIX No. 3, March 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXIX No. 4, April 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXIX No. 5, May 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. LXXXIX No. 6, June 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XC No. 2, August 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XC No. 3, September 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XC No. 4, October 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XC No. 5, November 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XC No. 6, December 1937 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCI No. 1, January 1938 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCIII No. 1, January 1939 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCIII No. 2, February 1939 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCIV No. 5, November 1939 (Box 13)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCVII No. 1, January 1941 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCVIII No. 2, August 1941 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCVIII No. 4, October 1941 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCVIII Nos. 5, 6, November-December 1941 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCIX No. 1, January 1942 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCIX No. 4, April 1942 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. XCIX Nos. 5, 6, May-June 1942 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. C No. 1, July 1942 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. C No. 2, August 1942 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. C No. 4, October 1942 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. C Nos. 5, 6, November-December 1942 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CI No. 1, January 1943 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CI No. 3, March 1943 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CI No. 4, April 1943 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CI Nos. 5, 6, May-June 1943 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CII No. 1, July 1943 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CII No. 2, August 1943 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CII No. 3, September 1943 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CII No. 4, October 1943 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CII Nos. 5, 6, November-December 1943 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CIII Nos. 1, 2, January-February 1944 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CIII No. 3, March 1944 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CIII No. 4, April 1944 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CIII No. 5, May 1944 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CIII No. 6, June 1944 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CIV Nos. 1, 2, July-August 1944 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CIV Nos. 3, 4, September-October 1944 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CIV Nos. 5, 6, November-December 1944 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CV Nos. 3, 4, March-April 1945 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CV Nos. 5, 6, May-June 1945 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CVI Nos. 1, 2, July-August 1945 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CVI Nos. 3, 4, September-October 1945 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CVI Nos. 5, 6, November-December 1945 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CVII Nos. 1, 2, January-February 1946 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal vol. CVII Nos. 3, 4 (published September), March-April 1946 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CVII Nos. 5, 6 (published November), May-June 1946 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CVIII Nos. 1-3 (published January 1947), July-September 1946 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CIX Nos. 1-3, July 1947 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CIX Nos. 4-6, October 1947 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CX Nos. 4-6, April 1948 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXI Nos. 1-3, July 1948 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXI Nos. 4-6, September 1948 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXIII, June 1949 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXIV Nos. 1-3, September 1949 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXIV Nos. 4-6, December 1949 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXVII Part 1, March 1951 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXVII Part 2, June 1951 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXVII Part 3, September 1951 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXVII Part 4, December 1951 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXVIII Part 3, September 1952 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXVIII Part 4, December 1952 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXIX Part 3, September 1953 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXX Part 1, March 1954 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXX Part 2, June 1954 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXX Part 3, September 1954 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXX Part 4, December 1954 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXXI Part 1, March 1955 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXXI Part 3, September 1955 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXXI Part 4, December 1955 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXXII Part 1, March 1956 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXXII Part 2, June 1956 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXXII Part 3, September 1956 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. CXXII Part 4, December 1956 (Box 14)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 139 Part 1, February 1973 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 139 Part 2, June 1973 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 139 Part 3, October 1973 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 140 Part 1, February 1974 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 140 Part 2, June 1974 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 140 Part 3, October 1974 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 141 Part 1, March 1975 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 141 Part 2, July 1975 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 141 Part 3, November 1975 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 142 Part 1, March 1976 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 142 Part 2, July 1976 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 142 Part 3, November 1976 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 144 Part 3, November 1978 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 143 Part 1, March 1977 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 143 Part 2, July 1977 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 143 Part 3, November 1977 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 144 Part 1, March 1978 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 144 Part 2, July 1978 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 145 Part 1, March 1979 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 145 Part 2, July 1979 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 145 Part 3, November 1979 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 146 Part 1, March 1980 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 147 Part 3, November 1981 (Box 15)
  - The Geographical Journal Vol. 148 Part 1, March 1982 (Box 15)
- 4. The Literary Digest, 1917-1931
  Series contains issues of The Literary Digest.
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 6. Whole No. 1399, February 10, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 8. Whole No. 1401, February 24, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 10. Whole No. 1403, March 10, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 11. Whole No. 1404, March 17, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 12. Whole No. 1405, March 24, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 13. Whole No. 1406, March 31, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 14. Whole No. 1407, April 7, 1919 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 15. Whole No. 1408, April 14, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 16. Whole No. 1409, April 21, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 18. Whole No. 1411, May 5, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 20. Whole No. 1413, May 19, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 21. Whole No. 1414, May 26, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 25. Whole No. 1418, June 23, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 54, No. 26. Whole No. 1419, June 30, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 2. Whole No. 1421, July 14, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 5. Whole No. 1424, August 4, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 7. Whole No. 1426, August 18, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 17. Whole No. 1436, October 27, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 18. Whole No. 1437, November 3, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 21. Whole No. 1440, November 24, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 22. Whole No. 1441, December 1, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 23. Whole No. 1442, December 8, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 24. Whole No. 1443, December 15, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 25. Whole No. 1444, December 22, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 55, No. 26. Whole No. 1445, December 29, 1917 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 1. Whole No. 1446, January 5, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 2. Whole No. 1447, January 12, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 3. Whole No. 1448, January 19, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 4. Whole No. 1449, January 26, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 5. Whole No. 1450, February 2, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 6. Whole No. 1451, February 9, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 7. Whole No. 1452, February 16, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 8. Whole No. 1453, February 23, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 9. Whole No. 1454, March 2, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 10. Whole No. 1455, March 9, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 12. Whole No. 1457, March 23, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 13. Whole No. 1458, March 30, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 14. Whole No. 1459, April 6, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 56, No. 15. Whole No. 1460, April 13, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 57, No. 3. Whole No. 1461, April 20, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 57, No. 4. Whole No. 1462, April 27, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 57, No. 5. Whole No. 1463, May 4, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 57, No. 7. Whole No. 1465, May 18, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 57, No. 8. Whole No. 1466, May 25, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 57, No. 9. Whole No. 1467, June 1, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 57, No. 10. Whole No. 1468, June 8, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 57, No. 11. Whole No. 1469, June 15, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 57, No. 12. Whole No. 1470, June 22, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 57, No. 13. Whole No. 1471, June 29, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 1. Whole No. 1472, July 6, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 2. Whole No. 1473, July 13, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 3. Whole No. 1474, July 20, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 4. Whole No. 1475, July 27, 1918 (Box 16)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 5. Whole No. 1476, August 3, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 6. Whole No. 1477, August 10, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 7. Whole No. 1478, August 17, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 8. Whole No. 1479, August 24, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 9. Whole No. 1480, August 31, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 10. Whole No. 1481, September 7, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 11. Whole No. 1482, September 14, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 12, Whole No. 1483, September 21, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 58, No. 13. Whole No. 1484, September 28, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 59, No. 1. Whole No. 1485, October 5, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 59, No. 2. Whole No. 1486, October 12, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 59, No. 3. Whole No. 1487, October 19, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 59, No. 4. Whole No. 1488, October 26, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 59, No. 6. Whole No. 1490, November 9, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 59, No. 7. Whole No. 1491, November 16, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 59, No. 8. Whole No. 1492, November 23, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 59, No. 9. Whole No. 1493, November 30, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 59, No. 12. Whole No. 1496, December 21, 1918 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 60, No. 3. Whole No. 1500, January 18, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 60, No. 5. Whole No. 1502, February 1, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 60, No. 6. Whole No. 1503, February 8, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 60, No. 7. Whole No. 1504, February 15, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 60, No. 8. Whole No. 1505, February 22, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 60, No. 9. Whole No. 1506, March 1, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 60, No. 10. Whole No. 1507, March 8, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 60, No. 11. Whole No. 1508, March 15, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 60, No. 12. Whole No. 1509, March 22, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 60, No. 13. Whole No. 1510, March 29, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 1. Whole No. 1511, April 5, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 2. Whole No. 1512, April 12, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 3. Whole No. 1513, April 19, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 4. Whole No. 1514, April 26, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 5. Whole No. 1515, May 3, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 6. Whole No. 1516, May 10, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 7. Whole No. 1517, May 17, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 8. Whole No. 1518, May 24, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 9. Whole No. 1519, May 31, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 10. Whole No. 1520, June 7, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 11. Whole No. 1521, June 14, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 12. Whole No. 1522, June 21, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 61, No. 13. Whole No. 1523, June 28, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 2. Whole No. 1525, July 12, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 3. Whole No. 1526, July 19, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 4. Whole No. 1527, July 26, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 5. Whole No. 1528, August 2, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 6. Whole No. 1529, August 9, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 7. Whole No. 1530, August 16, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 8. Whole No. 1531, August 23, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 9. Whole No. 1532, August 30, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 11. Whole No. 1534, September 13, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 12. Whole No. 1535, September 20, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 62, No. 13. Whole No. 1536, September 27, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 63, No. 1. Whole No. 1537, October 4, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest Vol. 63, No. 6. Whole No. 1542, November 8, 1919 (Box 17)
  - The Literary Digest 1931 Atlas of the World (Box 17)
- 5. Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, 1944-1949; 1 box
  Series contains issues of Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living.
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, October 1944 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, November 1944 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, December 1944 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, March 1945 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, April 1945 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, May 1945 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, June 1945 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, July 1945 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, August 1945 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, September 1945 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, October 1945 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, November 1945 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, December 1945 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, January 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, February 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, March 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, April 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, May 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, July 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, August 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, September 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, October 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, November 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, December 1946 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, January 1947 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, April 1947 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, May 1947 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, June 1947 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, July 1947 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, August 1947 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, September 1947 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, October 1947 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, November 1947 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, May 1948 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, June 1948 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, July 1948 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, August 1948 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, September 1948 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, October 1948 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, November 1948 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, January 1949 (Box 18)
  - Gourmet: The Magazine of Good Living, December 1949 (Box 18)
- 6. Asia, 1920-1938; 1 box
  Series contains issues from Asia.